https://aak.com/about-us/terms-and-conditions/

Available jobs
General Applications (Submit CV)
Terms and conditions
You are here:
You are here:Terms and conditions AAK.com
Access to and use of this AAK AB site is subject to the following terms and conditions and the laws of Sweden.
By accessing our website, you accept the terms and conditions set out herein below, and you should check these terms and conditions each time you visit the page. If you do not accept our terms and conditions for using this website, we ask you not to use this website. Other websites for companies in the AAK group may contain additional terms and you should read them separately.
Intellectual Property Rights
Copyright © AAK AB 2005-2020. All rights reserved. All copyright and other intellectual property rights in all text, images, sound, software and other materials on this site are owned by AAK AB and affiliated companies or are included with permission of the relevant owner. References to affiliates or affiliated companies shall include all members of the AAK Group.
You are permitted to browse this site and to reproduce extracts by way of printing, downloading to a hard disk and by distribution to other people but, in all cases, for non-commercial, informational and personal purposes only. No reproduction of any part of the site may be sold or distributed for commercial gain nor shall it be modified or incorporated in any other work, publication or site, whether in hard copy or electronic format, including posting to any other site. No other licence or right is granted.
All trademarks displayed on this site are either owned or used under licence by AAK AB and its affiliates.
Content
The information on this site has been included in good faith but is for general informational purposes only. It should not be relied on for any specific purpose and no representation or warranty is given as regards its accuracy or completeness. The price of shares and the income derived from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested. Past performance is not necessarily a guide to future performance.
Neither AAK AB nor any affiliates nor their or their affiliates' officers, employees or agents shall be liable for any loss, damage or expense arising out of any access to or use of this site or any site linked to it including, without limitation, any loss of profit, indirect, incidental or consequential loss.
We reserve the right to make any changes and corrections to this site as and when we consider it appropriate and without notice.
Availability of products
Reference to any product or service on the site does not constitute an offer to sell or supply that product or service and does not mean that the product or service is available in all countries or that the name, description or specification of the product or service will be the same as that included on the site. Specific advice concerning the availability and suitability of any particular product or service should be sought from the local AAK affiliate or distributor concerned.
Submissions of Data
When submitting information or personal information to us, you warrant and consent to our use of such information and personal information without compensation without violating anyone's rights.
Personal Data Protection
Personal data provided to us through this website will only be used in accordance with our Data privacy information. Please read before submitting information to us.
Contact
If you have any questions or comments about the content of these terms and conditions, you are welcome to contact us at comm@aak.com.
Learn more
Data privacy information
AKK is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Read our information on what type of personal data we collect and how we process such data and your rights against us as an individual.
Cookies
We use cookies to give you the best experience when visiting our website.
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, U.S.
